Curriculum Vitae

Personal information

First name(s) / Surname(s)

Li Wang 王利

Address(es)

42 Hankinson Road, BH9 1HW, Bournemouth, Dorset, U.K.

Mobile

+44 - 07732563454

E-mail

lwang@bournemouth.ac.uk/liwang1991@outlook.com

Nationality Date of birth

Chinese

04/04/1991

Gender

Personal Statements

I am currently a PhD candidate (expected graduation is Sep 2020s) of National Centre for Computer Animation at Bournemouth University, UK. I received my MEng and BSci degrees from Department of Computer Science and Technology at Jilin University, China in 2016 and 2013, respectively. Then I got CSC scholarship to support my 4-year PhD study at Bournemouth University.

Research Background

Research topic and research work

My research areas are Computer Vision and Computer Graphics, and PhD research topic is image style transfer based on Convolutional Neural Networks. I focus on the photographic style transfer and video stabilization for arbitrary artistic style transfer using deep learning technique.

Previous research projects include 3D reconstruction of human body skeleton for RNLI lifeboat project, contour detection and image segmentation.

Papers Published

- 1, Li Wang, Zhao Wang, Xiaosong Yang, Shi-Min Hu, Jianjun Zhang. Photographic Style Transfer. The Visual Computer, pp 1-15, 2018.
- 2, Li Wang, Nan Xiang, Xiaosong Yang, Jianjun Zhang. Fast Photographic Style Transfer based on Convolutional Neural Networks. *Proceedings of CGI 2018*, pages 67-76.
- 3, Xiang, N., Wang, L., Jiang, T., Li, Y., Yang, X. and Zhang, J., Single-image mesh reconstruction and pose estimation via generative normal map. pp 79-84, 2019.
- 4, Xiangjiu Che, Li Wang, Xiaoxin Guo. Improved Boundary Detection based on Multi-scale Cues Fusion. Journal of Jilin University(Engineering and Technology Edition), 2018, 48(5): 1621-1628.
- 5, Xiangjiu Che, Li Wang, Xiaoxin Guo. An Improved Edge Detection Method Using Adaptive Threshold, Transactions on Edutainment XII, pages 142-151, 2016.

Personal Capacities

Python, C/C++, Matlab, Torch/PyTorch, Ubuntu/Windows

Education

Apr 2017 - Oct 2017

Visiting scholar in Graphics & Geometric Computing Group at Tsinghua University, China Under the supervision of Prof. Shi-Min Hu

Sep 2016 - present

PhD student of National Centre for Computer Animation

Bournemouth University, UK

Jilin University, China

Sep 2009 - Jun 2016

Supervisors: Prof. Jianjun Zhang and Dr. Xiaosong Yang MEng and BSci in Computer Science and Technology

Supervisor: Prof. Xiangjiu Che.

Selected Honours and awards

2015, Huawei Postgraduate Scholarship.

2015, National Postgraduate Scholarship.

Work experience

Aug 2019 - Nov 2019 Jan 2013 - May 2013

Intern R&D Programmer at ITware (Hungary), SensorID (Italy) and University of Malaga (Spain) Intern R&D Programmer at IBM (China) Investment Co., Ltd

Responsibilities

Under direction of software engineer, solve Platform product bugs and implement middle complex projects

Hobbies Badminton



